Professional Summary

4+ years of experience in Testing as Associate Software Engineer.

Strong experience in working with Java, Python, Selenium, Cucumber, TestNG, JUnit BDD, Automation Testing, HTMLS, CSS3, JavaScript, Manual Testing, Git.

Quick learner and good team player.

Collaboration with development teams.

Ability to perform well under pressure to meet deadlines.

Possess strong analytical and problem-solving skills.

Well-regarded quantitative skills, Self-motivated and hardworking.

Work Experience

Working as Associate Software Engineer in Capgemini (Pune) from May 2022 to till date.

Worked as Software Engineer in Global Edge Software Itd. (Port Louis, Mauritius) from April 2020 to May 2022.

Education

MTech appearing from SVCET, Aurangabad.

BE in 2020 from ICEEM, Aurangabad.

Technical Skills

recimiear Giane	
Operating System	Windows XP & above Versions.
Languages	Java, Python.
Technical Specialization	Selenium, Junit, TestNG, Cucumber.
Scripting Languages	Python, Java, HTMLS, CSS3, JavaScript.
IDE	Eclipse, IntelliJ
Database	TestNG, Cucumber, SQL Server, NoSQL.
Cloud	Azure, AWS
Observability Tools	Kibana
Other Tools	JIRA, Test Rail, QTest, PractiTest, Gherkin.

Project Details

Project ; MCR E-40 (Duration: August 2022 - till date) Client (Olympus, Japan)

Company ; Capgemini

Team Size ; 10

Environment ; Test cases and Test Plans, Pass/Fail Judgement Criteria, Database Access, Test Environment, Test Data.